♪
[ANNE]
Wake up! Mythril Lid Pod!
Ah, what now?
[ANNE]
I got to see Challe yesterday!
[gasps] Did you, really?
And when I told him that
I'll be able to set him free
if I'm successful
at my job here,
he said he would wait for me!
[MYTHRIL]
He did? That's wonderful!
I thought he'd say, "Go away,
I don't need your help,"
so this is a surprise!
[gasps]
Having to be
that girl's companion
must really be unbearable.
She might be making him
do sordid things
we can't even imagine.
Um, what do you mean by sordid?
Don't worry about it!
[grunts]
Let's rebuild this place
as quickly as we can
and then rescue
Challe Fen Challe!
[ANNE]
Oh, right.
[birds chirping]
[men gasp]
Hmm.
- [NADIR] A girl.
- [Anne gasps]
And a fairy too!
[yelps]
What's your problem?
- [grunts]
- [NADIR] Hey, come out!
I've never seen a fairy
as small as you!
Let me look at you!
Please? Please?
Easy, Nadir.
That's quite enough.
Ah! Looks like everyone's here.
♪
Aren't you going to
introduce us, Elliot?
I was about to.
This is Anne Halford.
Starting today,
she'll be working here
as our very own
Head of Artisans.
And...
this fairy is her helper,
Mythril Lid Pod.
[grunts]
- Hmm?
- [KING] Wait, Halford?
The one who made a confection
for the former Duke of Philax?
- [Mythril whimpers]
- [ELLIOT] One and the same!
And, as of this year,
she's become
a silver sugar master!
Are you serious?
But why would someone so amazing
work here?
And she's a girl, at that!
[gasps and sighs]
[KING]
So, Mr. Glen approved this?
Yes.
[KING] Then who am I to object?
Hello, there. My name is King.
That's your name?
Well, I forgot my real name
some time ago.
I see.
It's an honor to meet you, King.
Huh? What's this?
Huh? A handshake?
[KING]
Oh. Yes, of course! A handshake!
[King grunts]
Uh...
And my name's Nadir.
So, will you come out now?
- [MYTHRIL] No!
- Mm...
A wise decision, little fairy.
My name is Valentine.
It's lovely to meet you.
[ANNE] Nice to meet you, too.
[ELLIOT]
Oh, Orland's here! Perfect!
So, now that you've met
all five of our workers,
we're at your service,
Miss Head of Artisans!
[chuckles]
[ANNE] Let's see.
- Where to start?
- Hey.
[ANNE] Oh, dear,
I don't really have
a clear understanding
of what I've agreed to.
Um, for now,
please continue your work
from yesterday.
- [NADIR] Sure!
- [KING] Will do.
- [ORLAND] Hmm.
- [VALENTINE] Right.
[metal clatters]
[Anne sighs]
Anne, what should I do?
Perhaps you could
get a little bit
of the cleaning done?
Leave it to me! [grunts]
[ANNE]
In the meantime,
I'll assess the situation!
♪
My, he's very talented.
Mr. Langston,
what sort of commission are you
working on at the moment?
Hm?
Don't bother
with the formalities.
There's no need to say Mr.
Oh. All right then.
So, what's that?
[ORLAND]
It's an order from a shop owner.
Apparently,
it's for their son's birthday.
[ANNE]
I see, so the son likes horses?
[ORLAND]
I wouldn't know.
I suggested a few ideas
and they chose a horse.
[ANNE] Did they say why?
[ORLAND]
Was I supposed to ask them?
[ANNE] There may be something
they'd like better.
Or perhaps there's a specific
type of horse they'd prefer.
[ORLAND] Honoring
the customer's every whim
doesn't always make
for a quality product.
[gasps]
[ORLAND] We employ all of our
skill to make what speaks to us.
Otherwise,
we can't create anything good.
[ANNE] I always thought giving
the customer what they want
was the best way.
♪
[gasps]
- It's lovely!
- [gasps]
The color is so nice!
Ah! You don't have to get
so close, you know!
Huh? Oh, pardon me!
[NADIR] Maybe Anne should start
wearing men's clothes.
Maybe I should punch you.
[ANNE] It seems like
he's uncomfortable around women.
- [VALENTINE] Excuse me.
- Yes?
[VALENTINE] I've finished
maintenance on the tools.
What's next?
Do we have more orders?
No, only two.
In that case,
could you assist
one of the other artisans?
Oh, I could never do that.
It's their work, after all.
[ANNE]
But it would be faster that way.
It isn't right to interfere
with another person's work.
[gasps]
[ANNE] I thought it was normal
for everyone in a workshop
to collaborate.
Uh...
[ANNE] Is there something
strange about what I said?
So, each of you completes
the task assigned to you
on your own?
Well, yes. We're artisans.
We take ownership of our work.
Then what
is the Head of Artisans
supposed to do?
[ORLAND] Manage the supply,
deal with clients,
and of course,
you'll assess
every sugar confection
that we produce
to determine
whether it might bring shame
upon the Paige Workshop.
Did you say shame?
We can't deliver work that
tarnishes the name of Paige.
Therefore, it's imperative that
you have us make corrections
if the product is lacking.
But, if the piece
is not an embarrassment,
you will approve it.
Then Mr. Glen will give it
the main workshop's seal.
That's your job
as Head of Artisans.
[ANNE] That's very different
from my experience so far.
How odd.
- Hello.
- [WOMAN] Hm?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Anne Halford.
Oh, hello there, miss.
My name is Dana
and this one's name is Hal.
You two look
practically identical!
- I imagine you must be siblings?
- [DANA] Yes.
Apparently, we were born
from the very same tree
at the exact same moment,
so in human terms,
I believe you would say
that we were twins.
[ANNE] Oh, really?
I didn't realize fairies
could be twins too!
Have you two had dinner yet?
I would be happy
to have you join me.
[DANA] Oh, no, we couldn't!
This table is only
for artisans and family.
[ANNE]
We all live in the same house!
That's family enough, isn't it?
[DANA]
No, not in the slightest!
We're fairies, after all.
Please excuse us!
- [ELLIOT] What a shame!
- [gasps]
Turned you down, huh?
Mr. Collins.
I'm sure you amazed everyone
on your first day
at the workshop.
So, what did you think of it,
Anne?
Hmm.
[ANNE] I learned a lot
about this place today.
The artisans make
what they want,
and they don't help each other.
Everyone takes responsibility
for their own work.
That's how it's been at Paige
for 300 years now.
Mr. Glen drills that
into all our heads
more than anything else.
It sounds nice in theory,
except...
Go on.
I don't know,
it just bothers me somehow.
[scoffs]
Well, since I was the one
who put you in this position,
got some time?
[thuds]
[ANNE] What's that?
[ELLIOT] Promissory notes.
[ANNE] You mean debts?
[ELLIOT] Right,
for about 10,000 cress,
with this land as collateral.
[ANNE] Did you say 10,000?
It's left over
from the last headmaster.
If it's not paid off this year,
we will lose half of this place.
[ANNE] Can you afford it?
No.
Which is why I went out to try
and negotiate again today.
Oh, by the way, don't tell.
[ANNE] Don't tell Mr. Glen?
He knows we're in debt
obviously,
but not that we're having
a difficult time paying it back.
And because of his illness,
the lenders are becoming
concerned
about the future
of the workshop.
That's awful.
You said earlier that something
didn't sit right with you.
[ANNE] I did.
[ELLIOT]
Well, I have opinions myself.
Huh?
None of us want
to turn our backs on Mr. Glen,
but something's gone wrong here.
I've given it a lot of thought,
and I still can't put my finger
on what the problem is.
Eh, I'll pay off
the debt somehow.
As for you, Anne,
just do what you think is best
like the first
silver sugar master.
You keep talking about that!
What is it
you're trying to tell me?
[CHALLE] You're dining alone?
Why not join the others?
[BRIDGET] That's simple.
I prefer to spend my time alone
with you.
[CHALLE] And yet,
your expression looks lonely.
[BRIDGET] I'm not lonely at all.
Hold me, Challe.
♪
Carry me to bed.
Now lay me down carefully.
Stroke my hair.
Stay till I fall asleep.
Please don't go
to see that girl.
Stay with me and only me.
[door opens]
- [CHALLE] Stare all you like...
- [gasps]
...nothing's going to happen.
[gasps]
[screams]
You scared me!
I thought you couldn't sneak out
or Miss Bridget would make you
do more sordid things!
- Sordid?
- Well,
that's what Mythril Lid Pod
told me, anyway.
Mythril Lid Pod
has a wild imagination.
She's a normal girl.
She's not forcing you
to do things?
No, she's not.
I'm so glad.
I'm going to work hard.
Just hold on.
♪
What... What's the matter?
Nothing.
Are you forming an opinion
about all these?
[chuckles]
Orland's work carries
a certain sense
of power and strength.
He's very quiet
and a little hard to approach
sometimes
but I can tell he cares
about his creations.
This one is by King,
who seems like a sincere person.
He's awkward around women
for some reason, but...
his confections still have
such a romantic feeling to them!
Don't you think it's beautiful?
They've both done
excellent work,
but we've only got
these two commissions right now.
I wonder why business
has gotten slow.
Hm? What's wrong?
Nothing.
- [door slams]
- [BRIDGET] Challe!
I asked you
not to see her again!
You didn't ask for that,
you ordered,
and I don't intend to obey you.
Do what you must.
[BRIDGET] You're saying
you won't consider my feelings?
[CHALLE] You are my master now.
And that means,
just as there's no expectation
for you to consider my feelings,
I can't think of any reason
to consider yours, either.
Is that so?
Well then,
I suppose there's not
a single person in the world
who cares how I feel.
[sniffles]
In that case...
you are to be punished!
- Wait!
- It's all right, Anne!
No, Challe, I don't want
anything to happen to you!
So meddlesome.
[panting]
- [crashes]
- [Bridget sniffling]
It's not here.
[panting]
[BRIDGET] Only I know
about this hiding place.
[Bridget sniffling]
So, who,
who could've stolen it?
[ELLIOT] If you mean the wing,
Mr. Glen has it.
[gasps]
What? Why is it with my father?
[GLEN]
Bridget.
Listen, someone came
and placed the wing
by my pillow,
so I'll say this now.
Going forward,
the wing will remain in my care.
Whoever left it with me probably
feels that it's for the best.
Why, Father?
You said it was all right
until I get married!
I can no longer tolerate
the way you're acting.
Locking that fairy in your room,
forbidding that he spend time
with anyone but yourself.
Really, dear, it's as though
you've become obsessed!
[groans]
Bridget,
I beg you to be sensible!
Whose daughter are you?
[Bridget sniffles]
I don't care!
Does this mean
that you're my new master?
Yes, I am,
and your orders are to interact
with Bridget in moderation.
There's no need to respond
to her every demand,
but please don't do anything
that would hurt her.
But, Mr. Glen, Challe doesn't...
I will decide
what happens to him now.
[Mythril gasps]
[MYTHRIL]
You actually got your wing back?
Not quite. It's just that
Mr. Glen has it instead of her.
[MYTHRIL] But you can go
where you please now!
What a torturous existence!
Letting that miserable woman
have her way with you,
all day and night!
Spare me
your moronic imaginings.
Well, we have a visitor,
so excuse me.
[MYTHRIL]
Right!
[GLEN] It's been
quite some time, Mr. Radcliffe.
[ANNE]
Mr. Radcliffe and Keith?
I'm glad you're faring better
than the rumors would suggest.
Oh, and, you've employed
a new silver sugar master.
[whimpers]
This is our Head of Artisans, actually.
Hm.
Judging by the timing
of her acceptance here,
are you taking part
in the selection
for
the Holy Beginnings Festival?
[ANNE]
Hm? Selection?
[GLEN]
Of course not.
My father rejected it.
[MARCUS]
I see.
I had a suspicion
that that might be your answer.
Ah, yes, and Powell's son
is here with me, as well.
My name is Keith, sir.
[GLEN]
I've heard talk about you.
They say
you've become a great artisan.
Thank you and I'm...
[sighs] sorry.
There's no reason to be.
You chose your path.
[ANNE]
Keith.
[door opens]
[ANNE]
I was surprised to see you!
[KEITH] Mr. Radcliffe
didn't give me much notice,
but I was wondering
how you've been doing.
Have you had any trouble, uh,
and how are things with Challe?
Oh, we're managing.
What about with you?
How are Kat and Jonas lately?
Actually, Mr. Hingley
has returned to his own shop.
Sadly, no one's been able
to get in touch with Jonas.
He never went back
to his old hometown.
Oh, is that so?
By the way, Keith,
can you tell me
about the selection
for
the Holy Beginnings Festival?
[KEITH] It's part
of the new-year celebrations.
As you know,
they set out sugar confections
in the Church
of Saint Lewiston Bell.
Workshops create
the sample pieces for it,
and one of them is selected
to produce the work that year.
[ANNE]
Oh, I see.
[KEITH]
It's a great honor to be picked,
and if the school successfully
delivers all the pieces,
the kingdom's religion awards
- 10,000 cress.
- [Anne gasps]
[KEITH] Then naturally,
that school becomes popular,
and more commissions come in.
Oh, it looks like
she has company.
- Her lover?
- Nadir!
It's nothing of the sort!
Don't say such awful things
to him!
Oh, there's nothing awful
about that.
Huh?
Oh.
I'm Keith Powell
of the Radcliffe Workshop.
Ah! So, you're him?
Yes, I understand.
Feel free to stay, then.
We should go.
[NADIR] Hm?
But... Well, um, bye!
Why'd they rush off?
[KEITH]
They had to,
because from their perspective,
I'm a traitor.
[ANNE] What do you mean?
♪
[KEITH] My father became
the Silver Sugar Viscount
while he was
with the Paige Workshop.
It really invigorated
this place.
So, after he passed away,
naturally, everyone assumed
that I would come to Paige
as he had done,
but in the end,
I chose the Radcliffe Workshop.
And then,
the rumor went around, saying,
"Powell has given up on Paige."
That caused the artisans
who worked here
to begin transferring
to other schools all at once.
That's just terrible.
But the truth is,
I hadn't given up on this place.
If I'd come here,
I would've been affected
by my father's influence.
I didn't want to follow
in his footsteps.
That was the only reason.
I endured it
while he held his position,
but even still, after he died,
I resented the idea
of being seen
as the son of Edward Powell.
The name Keith Powell
means something on its own.
- Don't worry.
- Hm.
It's not your fault
that the Paige Workshop
ended up this way,
and everyone here knows that.
But their feelings haven't
caught up yet, that's all.
Given some time,
that resentment will go away.
♪
[KEITH]
Thank you, Anne. Truly.
[ANNE] If we can turn
this place around,
then maybe Keith
will stop blaming himself,
and the artisans
will accept him again.
I have to succeed!
[MARCUS]
Keith! It's time!
[KEITH]
Right!
We're leaving so soon?
I wonder
if Mr. Radcliffe is worried.
The selection's
only half a month away.
[ANNE]
The selection.
- Oh, wait, that's it!
- [gasps]
Uh?
Thank you so much!
Of course.
I'm not too certain
what I did for you,
but still, you're very welcome.
[ANNE] Yes, if we win,
more people will notice us.
And we'll get 10,000 cress!
What Mr. Collins said,
and the things
that were weighing on my mind,
it could be!
[knocking on door]
I have a request.
I would like for our workshop
to take part
in this year's
festival selection.
If we do, it might help us
return to our former--
[GLEN]
No.
[gasps]
We will not participate.
But, sir...
♪